A Guide to the Papers of the Dean of Students,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1951 (Box-folder 68:6)
- Summer Session: General, 1950 (Box-folder 68:7)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1950 (Box-folder 68:8)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1949 (Box-folder 68:9)
- Suspension, Probations, Warnings, 1960 August-1961 June (Box-folder 68:10)
- Suspension, Probations, Warnings, 1959 February-1960 June (Box-folder 68:11)
- Suspension, Probations, Warnings, 1949 March-1956 March (Box-folder 68:12)
- Sweet Briar College, 1959 May-1961 May (Box-folder 68:13)
- Sweet Briar College, 1955 May-1958 October (Box-folder 68:14)
- Sweet Briar College, 1950 May-1954 September (Box-folder 68:15)
- Telephone Situation, 1951 January-1952 May (Box-folder 68:16)
- Texas Technological College, 1953 July-1956 July (Box-folder 68:17)
- Tile Damage, 1951 January-April (Box-folder 68:18)
- T.I.K.L.A., 1957 April-1961 May (Box-folder 68:19)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1959 January-1960 May (Box-folder 69:1)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1956 January-1958 December (Box-folder 69:2)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1954 January-1955 October (Box-folder 69:3)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1953 (Box-folder 69:4)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1952 (Box-folder 69:5)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1951 February-December (Box-folder 69:6)
- Traffic Control Office: General, 1949 March-1951 January (Box-folder 69:7)
- Traffic Control Office: Summer Session, 1954 September-1961 August (Box-folder 69:8)
- Trident Society: N.R.O.T.C., 1952 November-1953 November (Box-folder 70:1)
- Trigon Society, 1952 November-1956 March (Box-folder 70:2)
- Tuesday Concert Series, 1954 October-1956 April (Box-folder 70:3)
- Committee on Undergraduates, 1957 November-1959 October (Box-folder 70:4)
- Uniform Transcript Blanks, 1952 (Box-folder 70:5)
- University Artist Series, 1954 September-1956 April (Box-folder 70:6)
- University Chaperones, 1955-1956 February (Box-folder 70:7)
- University Press, 1953 (Box-folder 70:8)
- University Advisor to Students, 1959 (Box-folder 70:9)
- University Advisor to Students, 1958 October-December (Box-folder 70:10)
- University Advisor to Students, 1958 April-September (Box-folder 70:11)
- University Advisor to Students, 1958 January-March (Box-folder 70:12)
- University Advisor to Students, 1957 October-December (Box-folder 70:13)
- University Advisor to Students, 1957 May-September (Box-folder 70:14)
- University Advisor to Students, 1957 January-April (Box-folder 70:15)
- University Advisor to Students, 1956 September-December (Box-folder 71:1)
- University Advisor to Students, 1956 January-August (Box-folder 71:2)
- University Advisor to Students, 1954 July-1955 December (Box-folder 71:3)
- University of Virginia Magazine, 1959 November-1960 February (Box-folder 71:4)
- "V" Club, 1954 (Box-folder 71:5)
- Varsity Grill, 1953 (Box-folder 71:6)
- Virginia Academy of Science Meeting, 1959 (Box-folder 71:7)
- Virginia Association of Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers, 1952 October-1959 June (Box-folder 71:8)
- Virginia Association of Guidance and Personnel Workers, 1950 March-1957 March (Box-folder 71:9)
- Virginia Christian Fellowship, 1952 (Box-folder 71:10)
- Virginia Military Institute, 1950 September-1952 October (Box-folder 71:11)
- Virginia Music Festival, 1950 January-1952 October (Box-folder 71:12)
- Virginia Players, 1952 March-1954 November (Box-folder 71:13)
- Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1951 November-1959 June (Box-folder 71:14)
- Virginia State College, 1957 (Box-folder 71:15)
- Virginia Vocational Guidance Association, 1953 (Box-folder 71:16)
- Walt's Grill, 1952 (Box-folder 71:17)
- Washington and Lee University, 1952 October-1956 February (Box-folder 71:18)
- Wemple, Ed, 1959 (Box-folder 71:19)
- William and Mary, College of, 1950 October-1955 July (Box-folder 72:1)
- Williams College, 1952 February-1953 November (Box-folder 72:2)
- Withdrawls, 1960 September-1961 June (Box-folder 72:3)
- Withdrawls, Enforced, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 72:4)
- Women's Student Association, 1950 (Box-folder 72:5)
- Women, Dean of, 1951-1959 (Box-folder 72:6)
- Woodrow Wilson School of Foreign Affairs, 1950 June-1955 October (Box-folder 72:7)
- WUVA Radio Station, 1951 September-1959 May (Box-folder 72:8)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1960 September-1961 August (Box-folder 72:9)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1959 August-1960 July (Box-folder 72:10)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1957 June-1959 April (Box-folder 72:11)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1955 June-1957 May (Box-folder 72:12)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1954 April-1955 April (Box-folder 73:1)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1953 (Box-folder 73:2)
- Young Men's Christian Association, 1951 September-1952 December (Box-folder 73:3)
- Young Men's Christian Association: Applicant File, 1952 August-1954 May (Box-folder 73:4)
- Young Republican Club, 1954 October-1955 October (Box-folder 73:5)
- Z Society, 1953 May-1958 February (Box-folder 73:6)